Thank you for watching!
Ha ha ha ha
I'm a little surprised, but aren't you
all from Tohoku?
Yes!
Tohoku is a tourist destination, so
there are many people who come for
sightseeing, but when you go sightseeing
or go home, there are many people who
buy stationery.
Hmm.
Certainly.
You buy your favorite stationery,
right?
Yes Yes Yes.
But there are times when you wonder if
this is delicious other than your
favorite.
There is.
Miyagi Prefecture is famous for
seafood, so there are many seafood
stations.
When you go to Sendai Station.
Oh yeah.
This time, I actually went to buy a
lunch box at Sendai Station after this.
Can you eat it?
Yeah!
Just lunch.
This time it's only seafood-type
stations.
Oh!
I can!
I'll say it again.
1, 2, 3!
Only seafood-type lunch boxes.
Oh, really cool!
Yeah!
I like seafood, so I'm happy.
There are many types.
I'm glad.
Actually, for example, I think there
are times when everyone comes from
various places at your live, so I was
very happy to find out that this was
delicious at that time.
I'm glad.
So I think I'll go to Sendai Station to
buy a lunch box.
Yes!
In this outfit?
Yes.
It's difficult.
I'm going to be a child.
You're going to be a child.
I came to Sendai Station.
Yeah!
We're here!
They're selling station food in the
back.
This time, only seafood.
Beef tongue! Beef tongue! Beef tongue!
Only seafood.
I'm so happy.
But is meat seafood?
It's not.
It's the best one so far.
Wow!
Eel!
I like eel.
Eel? Wow!
It's the last one.
Let's take it.
This is it.
Eel!
What else?
Harako rice is famous.
It's famous.
We chose the expensive one.
Of course.
It's a fresh rice.
This is expensive.
Let's take the expensive one.
Yeah!
Are you okay?
We didn't take it because of the price.
Sorry.
Let's take the shrimp.
It's not our money.
That's right.
Anago?
I want to eat anago and eel.
I want to eat different one.
Let's try different one.
Let's do it.
Anago.
I'll take the expensive one.
Wow!
It's a lot.
Don't look at it.
Let's pay from here.
Okay, I'll go.
Will you pay?
Thank you.
It's a cake.
It seems that she will buy it for us.
Thank you.
It's a money of others.
Please subscribe to this channel.
We've finished buying.
Yeah!
Thank you for the food.
We're going back.
Bye.
Thank you for watching!
So, let's eat one by one and tell us
your honest thoughts.
Be honest?
You're always honest, aren't you?
I'm sure.
I don't lie.
Then, let's eat one by one.
OK.
I chose this.
This is a oyster rice.
It looks delicious.
It smells good.
Let's eat!
It's good!
Is it?
I'll try the rice first.
This is it.
It's good.
I've never had this before.
This is good.
It's a revolution.
It's good.
I want to add cheese.
What?
This is good.
I want to make it warm.
I see.
It might be cold.
It's a bit cold.
It's good.
This is good.
I'll eat this.
Please try it.
This is the rice with sea urchin.
I didn't touch the sea urchin.
But, I could feel the sea urchin.
Where is the sea urchin?
The sea urchin is in Haseki.
I ate sea urchin for the first time in
my life in Hokkaido.
I've never eaten sea urchin in a good
sushi restaurant.
So, I'm not sure if this is a high-
class level.
The sea urchin is a high-class level.
I'm sorry.
Let's eat.
I'll eat this.
It's good.
The texture is...
The texture?
It's hard.
It's good.
It's good, but it's not as good as the
one in Hokkaido.
It's a bento.
That's right.
It's not as good as a bento.
It's good.
I think it's good for people who like
the taste of sea urchin.
It's good for a bento.
It's a bento.
It's a shrimp seasoning leaflet.
It's a shrimp.
I don't know the reason.
Shake it, shake it.
There are different kinds of eggs in
this.
Let's peel all the eggs.
To be honest.
It's thick.
Amazing.
Please subscribe to my channel.
It looks so good.
I agree.
I'm glad.
Let's eat.
Thank you for watching.
I think it depends on the person.
I ate shrimp and it was great.
I liked the egg with soup stock.
I also ate shrimp.
I think it would be great if it was not
shrimp.
No, it's not.
What is it?
I think it's different.
It's a little hard.
I think it's shrimp.
I think I like it more than vinegared
rice.
I think so, too.
It's not sour at all.
I don't know. Maybe because I ate it
together.
If you like vinegared rice, you'll like
it.
And if you want to try various things,
you'll like it.
I chose Harako rice.
To be honest, everything is normal so
far.
I didn't expect it.
I want to expect the quality of lunch
box.
I bought two similar things.
So, I'll compare them.
This is grilled harasu.
It's not Harako rice.
Harasu?
It's a little different.
It's a specialty of Hiyagi.
It's messed up.
This is common for lunch box.
I think this is great.
It's amazing.
This looks good.
Which one is better?
I'm going to eat this!
It's a little different.
Itadakimasu!
It's good!
Wow!
The salmon is good!
Wow, it's got a lot of fat.
The salmon roe is good too.
The salmon is so tender.
It's so tender.
It's not fishy at all.
Can I move on to the next one?
I'll try the salmon harase-yaki.
It's good.
The salmon flakes are good too.
I know.
Everything is good.
This one looks more fatty, so this one
has more fat.
It melts in your mouth.
Both of them are good.
This one is good.
It's not fatty.
I don't need to add any new soy sauce.
I want to eat this one.
I want to eat this one with a nice
bottle of rice.
With a hot rice.
This is good.
It's good.
I was expecting this one.
It was great.
It was good.
It's so good.
I like this one too.
I'm happy.
Let's eat salmon again.
Miyagi salmon hoshizushi.
Itadakimasu.
It's good.
Salmon has a lot of rice, so it's good.
I didn't do that much.
I just said selfish things.
But, the one before was better.
It was good to have a good impact.
Well, please tell us your reaction
after eating the Harukomushi.
The next is the eel Harukomushi.
This is the eel Harukomushi.
And this is the eel Harukomushi.
It looks good!
The eel is really juicy
and the eel is big
and there's a lot inside
It's really big
The eel
It's so good
It's so plump
The meat is so thick
It's so good
I think it could be a little more
flavorful
I think so too
Let's go to the next one
Can you tell the difference?
What does eel taste like?
Is it burnt?
It's burnt.
The taste of the sauce is unique.
The taste of the eel is still there.
You are not saying anything.
Do you want to say P?
You said too much.
I said too much.
She is so funny.
She is so funny suddenly.
I can't decide the answer.
Is this the end of the lunch box?
I'm full.
I bought beef tongue!
I bought the most expensive one!
I'll have the last one.
This is beef tongue.
Let's eat!
The reaction is different from before.
I'm going to eat it all.
It's hard to choose a beer.
Really?
I don't know.
What is this?
Each of you can choose one.
And you can give us your impression.
My best is...
Harako-meshi.
I like Harako-meshi.
I've tried many kinds of Harako-meshi.
But this is the best.
The most voted job in a month is....
Thank you for watching.
Heart.
I'll say it.
Cobblerikaya and Toro salmon!
Salmon roe is plump and I like fatty
part.
Toro salmon was so good.
My most voted job is....
Ebi nagi.
I'll say it.
I'm the same as Ruri.
Toro salmon was good and salmon roe was
good.
My most voted job is....
Kakimeshi!
I ate it first.
It was big and good.
Rice was good, too.
I want you to eat it, too.
My most voted job is....
Kakimeshi!
It's popular.
I like oysters.
So, I like oysters.
It was good.
My most voted job is....
Anago!
I like anago and I don't like fatty
part of fish.
Anago was plump and good.
It was mixed well.
Harako and Kakimeshi are popular.
I like the one with a lot of fillet.
I think you don't know which one is
which yet.
Why don't you say it?
I'm suffering from osteoporosis.
You're the 8th one who bought 8.
There are many kinds of bento in the
world.
I'm in a good mood today.
I'm in a good mood, too.
I didn't meet the expectations of
today.
I might meet them tomorrow.
That's all.
Please subscribe!
【The answer is...】
The 8th question is...
Ready, set, go!
Eel!
【The answer is...】
No...
I'm gonna cry.
I think this was the only one that
didn't work.
【The answer is...】
You failed to get just one right.
I think you failed.
I think I did.
I made a mistake, but I was able to get
it right.
I think you made a mistake in the
sauce.
I think I made a mistake.
I think I made a mistake in the sauce.
I want you to eat it.
Please tell me how you feel.
It's not good.
It's as I expected.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for watching!
So, this time we introduced seafood.
We will introduce more seafood for
those who come to Miyagi Prefecture.
I want to introduce the area where you
can eat souvenirs.
We will continue to introduce seafood
in the next video.
That's all for today.
Thank you for watching.
Thank you for the meal.